Guide to the A.I.R. Gallery Archives MSS.184
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Exhibition files
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions held at A.I.R. (see also Oversize)
    - Dotty Attie, Nov. 6-Dec. 1, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 399)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Dec. 4, 1976-Jan. 5, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 400)
    - "Invitational Show" Selected by Anne Healy, Jan. 8-Feb. 2, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 401)
    - A.I.R. Fifth Anniversary Show at PS1, Mar. 5-Apr. 9, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Kazuko, Mar. 5-30, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 403)
    - Pat Lasch, Apr. 2-27, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 404)
    - Donna Byars, Apr. 30-May 25, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 405)
    - "A.I.R. Invitational", May 28-June 28, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 406)
    - "Memorial Exhibition: Sakiko Ide", June 25-July 9, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 407)
    - Sari Dienes, Sep. 10-Oct. 5, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 408)
    - Mary Beth Edelson, Proposals for "Memorials to the 9,000,000 Women Burned as Witches in the Christian Era", Oct. 8-Nov. 2, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 409)
    - Blythe Bohnen, Nov. 5-Dec. 7, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 410)
    - Maude Boltz, Dec. 10, 1977-Jan. 11, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 411)
    - Sylvia Sleigh, Jan. 14-Feb. 8, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 412)
    - Daria Dorosh, Feb. 11-Mar. 8, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 413)
    - Patsy Norvell, Mar. 11-Apr. 5, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, Apr. 8-May 3, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 415)
    - Clover Vail, May 6-31, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 416)
    - "An Exhibition of Women Artists from Japan", June 3-July 1, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 417)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Sep. 9-Oct. 4, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 418)
    - Anne Healy, Oct. 7-Nov. 1, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 419)
    - Dotty Attie, Nov. 4-29, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 420)
    - Loretta Dunkelman, Dec. 9, 1978-Jan. 10, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 421)
    - Nancy Spero, Jan. 13-Feb. 7, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 422)
    - Pat Lasch, Feb. 10-Mar. 7, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 423)
    - Kazuko, Mar. 13-Apr. 4, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Louise Kramer, Apr. 7-May 2, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 425)
    - "Artists from Israel: An Exhibition of Works by Six Women", Sep. 6-22, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Ana Mendieta, Nov. 6-24, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Laurace James, Nov. 27-Dec. 15, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - "Members Group Exhibition: Holiday A.I.R.", Dec. 18, 1979-Jan. 5, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - "Performance Series", Jan. 29-Feb. 16, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - "Women Artist Performance Series: Ann Wilson", Jan. 29-Feb. 2, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - "Women Artist Performance Series: Mimi Smith", Feb. 5-9, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Daria Dorosh, Feb. 19-Mar. 8, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, Mar. 11-29, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Patsy Norvell, Apr. 1-19, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 436)
    - Clover Vail, Apr. 22-May 10, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Sari Dienes, May 13-31, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - "Speaking Volumes: Women Artists' Books" curated by Lucy Lippard, June 3-21, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - "Dialectics of Isolation: An Exhibition of Third World Women Artists of the United States", Sep. 2-20, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - Pat Lasch, Sep. 23-Oct. 10, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Oct. 14-Nov. 1, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - Dotty Attie, Nov. 4-22, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - "A.I.R. Group Show", Dec. 16, 1980-Jan. 3, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Elaine Reichek, Jan. 27-Feb. 14, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Loretta Dunkelman, Apr. 21-May 9, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 446)
    - Louise Kramer, May 12-30, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - "Sweden Comes to New York: An Exhibition of Six Swedish Women Artists", Sep. 8-26, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - "A.I.R. Group Show", Sep. 29-Oct. 17, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Mary Beth Edelson, Oct. 20-Nov. 7, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Ana Mendieta, Nov. 10-28, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Sarah Draney, Dec. 1-19, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - "Holiday Show of Festive Works", Dec. 22, 1981-Jan. 9, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 453)
    - "Sights Unseen" (curated by Sandi Fellman), Jan. 12-30, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 454)
    - "CHOICE: Inaugural Exhibition of National A.I.R. Affiliate Members", Feb. 2-20, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 455)
    - Daria Dorosh, Feb. 23-Mar. 13, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 456)
    - Patsy Norvell, Apr. 6-24, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 457)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, Apr. 27-May 15, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 458)
    - "View from Upstate" (curated by Loretta Dunkelman), June 8-26, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 459)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Oct. 19-Nov. 6, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 461)
    - Harmony Hammond, Nov. 9-27, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 462)
    - "Choice, Too: A.I.R. National Affiliate Members Exhibition", Nov. 30-Dec. 18, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 463)
    - "Annual Holiday Invitational Exhibition", Dec. 21, 1982-Jan. 8, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 464)
    - Louise Kramer, Jan. 11-29, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 465)
    - Howardena Pindell, Feb. 1-19, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 466)
    - Lenore Goldberg, Feb. 22-Mar. 12, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 467)
    - Anne Healy, Mar. 15-Apr. 2, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 468)
    - Loretta Dunkelman, Apr. 26-May 14, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 470)
    - Martha Ross Edelheit/Rosalind Schneider, May 17-June 4, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 471)
    - Donna Byars/Diane Farrell, June 7-25, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 472)
    - Kazuko, Sep. 6-24, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 473)
    - Dotty Attie, Sep. 27-Oct. 15, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 474)
    - Mary Beth Edelson, Oct. 18-Nov. 5, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 475)
    - Sari Dienes, Nov. 8-26, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 476)
    - Barbara Strasen, Nov. 29-Dec. 17, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 477)
    - "Third Annual Holiday Invitational Exhibition", Dec. 20, 1983-Jan. 7, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 478)
    - Carla Tardi, Jan. 10-28, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 479)
    - "Another Choice: Third National A.I.R. Gallery Affiliate Members Exhibition", Jan. 31-Feb. 18, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 480)
    - Harmony Hammond, Mar. 13-31, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 481)
    - "Expression: Recent Works by Women Artists" (curator: Elise Meyer), Apr. 3-21, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 482)
    - Judith Bernstein, Apr. 24-May 12, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 483)
    - Clover Vail, May 5-June 2, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 484)
    - "Detail: The Special Task: An Exhibition of Works by Women Architects", June 5-23, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 485)
    - Diane Farrell, Sep. 4-22, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 486)
    - "Women Artists of the '80s: New Talent", Sep. 25-Oct. 13, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 487)
    - Mary Grigoriadis, Oct. 16-Nov. 3, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 488)
    - "4th A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Member Exhibition", Nov. 6-24, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 489)
    - "Fourth Holiday Invitational Exhibit", Dec, 19, 1984-Jan. 5, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 490)
    - "Rachel bas-Cohain 1937-1982: Selected Works", Jan. 8-26, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 491)
    - Sydney Blum, Jan. 29-Feb. 16, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 492)
    - Elaine Reichek, Feb. 19-Mar. 9, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 493)
    - Louise Kramer, Mar. 12-30, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 494)
    - Nicole Jolicoeur, Apr. 2-18, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 495)
    - "Recent Works: Emily Cheng, Nancy Davidson, Fontaine Dunn", Apr. 23-May 11, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 496)
    - Lenore Goldberg, May 14-June 1, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 497)
    - Diane Samuels, June 4-22, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 498)
    - Helene Brandt, Sep. 17-Oct. 5, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 499)
    - Gerda Mayer Bernstein, Oct. 8-26, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 500)
    - "A.I.R. Members Exhibit 1985: Celebrating Our 13th Season", Oct. 29-Nov. 16, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 501)
    - Mary Weidner, Nov. 19-Dec. 7, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 502)
    - "Fifth Holiday Invitational Exhibit", Dec. 10, 1985-Jan. 4, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 503)
    - "Five Artists: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition", Jan. 7-25, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 504)
    - Elke Solomon, Jan. 28-Feb. 15, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 505)
    - Sandra Eisenstein, Feb. 18-Mar. 8, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 506)
    - Sari Dienes, Mar. 11-29, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 507)
    - Sarah Prentiss, Apr. 1-19, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 508)
    - Sarah Draney, Apr. 22-May 10, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 509)
    - "Another Dimension: Works from Vermont"/Amara Geffen, May 13-31, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 510)
    - "Women Photographers NOW", June 3-21, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 511)
    - Dea Trier Morch, June 24-July 5, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 512)
    - Rochelle Shicoff, Sep. 23-Oct. 11, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 513)
    - Dotty Attie/Mary Grigoriadis, Oct. 14-Nov. 22, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 514)
    - Kim Abeles, Oct. 15-Nov. 1, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 515)
    - Diane Samuels, Nov. 25-Dec. 13, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 516)
    - "Emerging Women Artists Series" (curator: Susan Putterman), Nov. 25-Dec. 13, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 517)
    - "Sixth Annual Holiday Invitational Exhibit", Dec. 16, 1986-Jan. 2, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 518)
    - "Five Artists: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition", Jan. 6-24, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 519)
    - "A.I.R. Group Show", Jan. 27-Feb. 14, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 520)
    - Patsy Norvell/Elaine Reichek, Feb. 17-Mar. 7, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 521)
    - Donna Byars, Mar. 31-Apr. 18, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 522)
    - Loretta Dunkelman, Apr. 21-May 9, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 523)
    - Lenore Goldberg/Marcia Godosky, Susan Miller, Maggie Poor, May 12-31, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 524)
    - "A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition", Oct. 13-31, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 525)
    - Susan Hambleton, Nov. 3-21, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 526)
    - "A.I.R. Group Exhibition: 9"/Cecilia Schmidt and Carole Spelic, Nov. 24-Dec. 12, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 527)
    - "7th Annual Holiday Invitational Exhibit", Dec. 15, 1987-Jan. 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 528)
    - Jane Haskell, Jan. 12-30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 529)
    - Elke Solomon/Irene Lipton, Louise Reiner, Barrie Karp, Feb. 2-20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 530)
    - "Artists Choose Artists"/Barrie Karp and Ruth Rothschild, Feb. 23-Mar. 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 531)
    - "Blue Angel: The Decline of Sexual Stereotypes in Post-Feminist Sculpture", Mar. 15-Apr. 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 532)
    - Daria Dorosh/Dale Emmett and Claire Leiberman, Apr. 5-23, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 533)
    - Sari Dienes/Rosemarie Maurer, Apr. 26-May 14, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 534)
    - Nancy Storrow/Abby Kavish, May 17-June 4, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 535)
    - "A.I.R. Invitational"/Olivia McCullough and Marsha Trattner, June 7-25, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 536)
    - "Affiliate Show", Sep. 17-Oct. 8, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 537)
    - Adeline Olmer and Ellen Weider/Suzanne Reese Horvitz, Oct. 11-29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 538)
    - Diane Samuels, Nov. 1-19, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 539)
    - Clover Vail/Lisa Sloane/Robin Nemlich, Nov. 22-Dec. 10, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 540)
    - "8th Annual Holiday Invitational", Dec. 14, 1988-Jan. 6, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 541)
    - Carol Ross/Nancy Miller and Arlene Rush, Jan. 10-29, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 542)
    - "Members' Show", Jan. 31-Feb. 18, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 543)
    - Mary Grigoriadis/Portland McCormick, Feb. 21-Mar. 11, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 544)
    - Gerda Mayer Bernstein/Mary Barringer and Diane Barwarski, Mar. 14-Apr. 1, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 545)
    - Lenore Goldberg and Rochelle Shicoff/Esther Podemski and Carol Waag (Apr. 4-22)/Christine Wade and Marina Izrailevich (Apr. 25-May 13), Apr. 4-May 13, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 546)
    - Carolyn Martin/Ellen Buljeta and Florence Sillen, May 16-June 3, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 547)
    - WARM Show/Jantje Visscher and Rebecca Martin, June 6-July 2, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 548)
    - "Outside New York: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibit", Sep. 19-Oct. 7, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 549)
    - Barbara Takenaga/Cordula Volkening, Oct. 10-28, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 550)
    - Nancy Azara/Lisa Collado, Oct. 31-Nov. 18, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 551)
    - Sharon Brant/Alda Amendola and Nancy Olivier, Nov. 21-Dec. 9, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 552)
    - "Beyond New York: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition", Dec. 12, 1989-Jan. 6, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 553)
    - Members' Show/Cynthia Fusillo and Dorothy Shamonsky, Jan. 9-27, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 554)
    - Elke Solomon/Penny Coleman, Jan. 30-Feb. 17, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 555)
    - Stephanie Bernheim, Feb. 20-Mar. 10, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 556)
    - Daria Dorosh/Sarah Savidge, Mar. 13-31, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 557)
    - Sari Dienes/Sherry Kerlin, Apr. 3-21, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 558)
    - Jane Haskell/Susanne Muel, Apr. 24-May 12, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 559)
    - Kathleen Schneider/Joan Fucillo, May 15-June 2, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 560)
    - "WARM/A.I.R."/Lynda Ray (Emerging Artist Program), June 5-23, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 561)
    - "Outside New York: A.I.R. Gallery National Affiliate Exhibition", Sep. 18-Oct. 6, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 562)
    - Elizabeth Munro Smith/Karen Yank, Oct. 9-27, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 563)
    - Carol Ross/Patricia Kieger/Karyn Meyer, Oct. 30-Nov. 17, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 564)
    - Nancy Storrow/Mary McDonnell, Nov. 20-Dec. 8, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 565)
    - "Children's Museum of the Arts", Jan. 8-26, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 567)
    - "Members Show"/"National Affiliates", Jan. 29-Feb. 16, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 568)
    - Ann Pachner/Adele Arner Shorr, Feb. 19-Mar. 9, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 569)
    - Louise Kramer/Pamela Arm, Mar. 12-30, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 570)
    - Lenore Goldberg/Joanna Pinsky, Apr. 4-20, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 571)
    - Rochelle Shicoff/Lissi Sigillo, Apr. 23-May 5, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 572)
    - "A.I.R. Print Portfolio: 'Women Making History 1976'"/Ursula Clark and Laurie Lea, Jan. 8-26, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 573)
    - Rachel bas-Cohain, June 4-22, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 574)
    - "National Affiliates", Sep. 16-Oct. 5, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 575)
    - Barbara Takenaga/Jeanne Flanagan, Oct. 8-26, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 576)
    - Sharon Brant/Barbara Pollack/"Who Cares About Feminism?: Art and Politics in the Nineties" panel, Oct. 29-Nov. 16, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 577)
    - "National Affiliates Show"/"Choice: A Show of Solidarity for Women's Reproductive Rights", Dec. 10, 1991-Jan. 4, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 578)
    - "Choice: A Show of Solidarity for Women's Reproductive Rights", Dec. 10, 1991-Jan. 4, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 579)
      contents of this folder derive from binder orig. stored with photo series in provenance
    - "Choice: A Show of Solidarity for Women's Reproductive Rights": photos, Dec. 10, 1991-Jan. 4, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 580)
      credit: Karen Bell
    - "Members Show"/Ann Glazer, Jan. 7-25, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 581)
    - Nancy Azara/Jantje Visscher, Jan. 28-Feb. 15, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 582)
    - Stephanie Bernheim, Feb. 18-Mar. 7, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 583)
    - Daria Dorosh/Ellen W. Kamerling, Mar. 10-28, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 584)
    - Sari Dienes/Margaret Krug, Mar. 31-Apr. 18, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 585)
    - Jane Haskell/May Savidge, Apr. 21-May 9, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 586)
    - Ann Sperry, May 12-June 3, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 587)
    - "Members Show"/Susan Stoltz, "Rather Be Dead Than Red" (June 11th)/"Wsex; reading" (June 18th), June 3-20, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 588)
    - "National Affiliates", Sep. 15-Oct. 3, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 589)
    - Carol Ross/Riva Lehrer, Oct. 6-24, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 590)
    - Elke Solomon/Rachel Selekman, Oct. 27-Nov. 14, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 591)
    - Cynthia Carlson/Ro Ulrich, Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 592)
    - "Holiday Invitational"/"National Affiliates", Dec. 8, 1992-Jan. 2, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 593)
    - "Holiday Invitational" insurance forms (A-L), Dec. 8, 1992-Jan. 2, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 593a.)
    - "Holiday Invitational" insurance forms (M-Z), Dec. 8, 1992-Jan. 2, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 593b.)
    - "Members Show"/Mary Klein, Jan. 5-23, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 594)
    - Barbara Roux/Lloyd Gunther Dallett, Jan. 26-Feb. 13, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 595)
    - Ann Pachner/Marilyn Crockett/"Lesbian and Gay Poets Series" (Feb. 17), Feb. 16-Mar. 6, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 596)
    - Stephanie Bernheim, Mar. 9-27, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 597)
    - "Members' Drawing Show"/Mary McDonnell, Mar. 30-Apr. 17, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 598)
    - Barbara Grinnell/Pat Howard, Apr. 20-May 8, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 599)
    - Janise Yntema, May 11-29, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 600)
    - Kathleen Schneider/Joyce Raimondo, June 1-19, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 601)
    - "National Affiliates", Sep. 14-Oct. 2, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 602)
    - Jessie Nebraska Gifford/Nana Nicola Olivas, Oct. 5-23, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 603)
    - "Women About Art: The Turnaround Year" (juried show), Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 604)
    - Carolyn Martin/Carol Massa, Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 605)
    - "National Affiliates Show"/Nancy White, Dec. 7, 1993-Jan. 2, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 606)
    - "Members Show"/Patricia Smith, Jan. 4-22, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 607)
    - "Women's Health", Feb. 16-Mar. 6, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 608)
    - Daria Dorosh/Sylvia Netzer, Mar. 9-27, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 609)
    - Stephanie Bernheim, Mar. 29-Apr. 16, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 610)
    - Sharon Brant/Sue Hettmansperger, Apr. 19-May 7, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 611)
    - Pat Lasch/Hui-Lin Chao, May 10-28, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 612)
    - "Photo Group Show"/Caren Raphael, May 31-June 25, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 613)
    - "National Affiliates", Sep. 13-Oct. 1, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 614)
    - Carol Ross/Kate Katomski, Oct. 4-22, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 615)
    - Barbara Roux/Hilda Daniel, Oct. 25-Nov. 12, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 616)
    - Nancy Azara, Nov. 15-Dec. 3, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 617)
    - "National Affiliates"/Lenore Goldberg, Dec. 6-31, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 618)
    - "Members Show"/Linda Tharp, Jan. 3-21, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 619)
    - Elke Solomon/Sandy Strauss, Jan. 24-Feb. 11, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 620)
    - Ann Pachner/Kristina Uusitalo, Feb. 14-Mar. 4, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 621)
    - Louise Kramer/Joanna McFarland, Mar. 7-25, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 622)
    - Regina Granne, Mar. 28-Apr. 15, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 623)
    - Stephanie Bernheim/Micaela Amato and Antonette Rosato, Apr. 18-May 6, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 624)
    - Janise Yntema/Nan Tull, May 9-27, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 625)
    - Tenesh Webber/Linda Kamille Schmidt, May 30-June 17, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 626)
    - "Members Group Show: Works on Paper", June 20-July 8, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 627)
    - "Member's Choice: Emerging Women Artists at A.I.R.", July 11-29, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 628)
    - "National Affiliate Exhibition", Sep. 12-30, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 629)
    - Daria Dorosh/L.L. Balmuth, Oct. 3-21, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 630)
    - Madeline Weinrib/Cynthia Willett, Oct. 24-Nov. 11, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 631)
    - Carolyn Martin/Mo Neal, Nov. 14-Dec. 2, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 632)
    - "National Affiliate Exhibition"/Jane Greer, Dec. 5-30, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 633)
    - "Members Show"/K. Webster, Jan. 2-20, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 634)
    - Jessie Nebraska Gifford/Ivy Dachman, Jan. 23-Feb. 10, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 635)
    - Beatrice Riese/Liz Surbeck Biddle, Feb. 13-Mar. 2, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 636)
    - Nancy Storrow/Eva Lee, Mar. 5-23, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 637)
    - Louise McCagg, Mar. 26-Apr. 13, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 638)
    - Sharon Brant/Cary Beth Cryor, Apr. 16-May 4, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 639)
    - Valerie Constantine, "Straw into Gold" (7 PM), May 5, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 640)
    - Alexandra Carmel/Susan Miller, May 7-25, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 641)
    - 2nd Biennial Exhibition (curator: Charlotta Kotik), May 28-June 15, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 642)
    - 2nd Biennial Exhibition (curator: Charlotta Kotik), May 28-June 15, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 643)
    - Group Show: "Drawings: Large and Larger", June 18-July 6, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 644)
    - MCAF Show: "Force of Habit" (curator: Alissa Schoenfeld), July 9-27, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 645)
    - "National Members' Exhibition", Sep. 7-28, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 646)
    - Carol Ross/Andrea Legge, "Fear of Flying", Oct. 1-19, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 647)
    - Sylvia Netzer, "Miasma Morph", Oct. 22-Nov. 9, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 648, Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 2)
    - Barbara Roux, "High Meadow"/Ursula Schneider, Nov. 12-30, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 649)
    - Lenore Goldberg/National Affiliates, Dec. 3-28, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 650)
    - A.I.R. Group Show/"A Composite Portrait: A.I.R. and the Women's Art Movement", Jan. 2-18, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 651)
    - Elke Solomon/Barbara Siegel, Jan. 21-Feb. 8, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 652)
    - Ann Pachner/L.L. Balmuth, Feb. 11-Mar 1, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 653)
    - Ann Sperry, Mar. 4-22, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 654)
    - Regina Granne/Leanne Corcoran, Mar. 25-Apr. 12, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 655)
    - Barbara Grinnell/Arden Scott, Apr. 15-May 3, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 656)
    - Janise Yntema/Frances Begley, May 6-24, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 657)
    - Beatrice Riese: "Obscure Words, Magic Squares"/Jane Greer, May 27-June 14, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 658)
    - Diyan Achjadi, "Learn to Recognize When..."/Ellen McMahon, June 17-July 5, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 659)
    - Rita Robillard/Gayle Tanaka, July 8-26, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 660)
    - "A.I.R. Gallery National Members Exhibition", Sep. 6-27, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 661)
    - Carolyn Martin/Bernice Ficek-Swenson, Sep. 30-Oct. 18, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 662)
    - "The Generations Show: Celebrating the 25th Anniversary", Oct. 21-Nov. 15, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 663)
    - Madeline Weinrib/Laetitia Hohneberg, Nov. 18-Dec. 6, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 664)
    - "National Members Exhibition"/Nancy Palmeri, Dec. 9, 1997-Jan. 3, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 665)
    - "Currents: Members Group Show"/"The Digital Print", Jan. 6-24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 666)
    - "The Digital Print" - artist agreement forms, Jan. 6-24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 667)
    - "The Digital Print" - artist response forms, Jan. 6-24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 668)
    - "The Digital Print" - receipts, Jan. 6-24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 669)
    - "The Digital Print" - Vernon Computer leasing contracts, Jan. 6-24, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 670)
    - Alex Carmel/Susan Carnahan, Jan. 27-Feb. 14, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 671)
    - Linda Levit/Nijole Kudrika, Feb. 17-Mar. 7, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 672)
    - Susan Bee, "Post-America"/Lynn Criswell, Mar. 10-28, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 673)
    - Michi Itami, "Recent Work", Mar. 31-Apr. 18, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 674)
    - Daria Dorosh, "Scraps and Shadows"/Elizabeth Hill, "A Biography", Apr. 21-May 9, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 675)
    - Jessie Nebraska Gifford/April Vollmer, May 12-30, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 676)
    - Angie Eng, "Drive In, Blind Spots and a Dead End"/Kim Waale, "Stagings", June 2-20, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 677)
    - Kathleen Schneider, "Toil and Spin"/Ann Ledy, June 23-July 11, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 678)
    - "A.I.R. Gallery Artists' Tribute to Tibet", July 14-Aug. 1, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 679)
    - "National Members Exhibition", Sep. 5-26, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 680)
    - Carol Kreeger Davidson/Hilary Lorenz, Sep. 29-Oct. 17, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 681)
    - Louise McCagg/Katinka Mann, Oct. 20-Nov. 7, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 682)
    - Carol Ross/Beverly Floyd, Nov. 10-28, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 683)
    - Third Biennial Juried Show (curator: Elizabeth Sussman), Dec. 1-19, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 684)
    - "Members Group Show"/"National Affiliates Exhibition", Jan. 5-23, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 685)
    - Judith Uehling, Jan. 26-Feb. 13, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 686)
    - Sylvia Netzer, Feb. 16-Mar. 6, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 687)
    - Lenore Goldberg, Mar. 9-27, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 688)
    - Regina Granne/Melisse Herman, Mar. 30-Apr. 17, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 689)
    - Elke Solomon/Marcia Hillis, Apr. 20-May 8, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 690)
    - Barbara Roux/Linda Schrank, May 11-29, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 691)
    - "Membership: Fellowship", June 1-19, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 692)
    - "Membership: Fellowship"/Elizabeth Zechel, June 1-19, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 693)
    - Members: "MACRO/micro"/Charmaine Wheatley, June 22-July 24, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 694)